uwcfs.com 2013-12-14

# Privacy policy | Mayzus Financial Services

Mayzus Financial Services Ltd (hereafter called "Mayzus Financial Services") considers you as its registered user and your privacy important. 

#### Mayzus Financial Services Privacy and Use of Personal Information

MayzusFS Ltd complies with the Data Protection Act 1998 with respect to information about its customers’ private information. We make every effort to conduct appropriate management and maintain accuracy and confidentiality of information. However, information that is already in the public domain is not considered confidential.   
You as our customer take full responsibility for informing us about any changes that may occur in your personal details such as change of address, or change of name. You confirm that you will inform us in writing about any such changes, and provide us with the photocopies of documentary evidence so that we can keep our records updated. 

#### 1\. The information you will provide us with is used

  * \- to facilitate Mayzus Financial Services services and ensure secure transaction processing;

  * \- to keep customer records updated;

  * \- for the smooth provision of our services and accurate administration of your account;

  * \- as data necessary for company management;

  * \- for statutory returns;

  * \- legal and regulatory compliance;

  * \- to check the identity of an individual or a business.

Please note that the service we provide for you may require us giving information to third parties such as 

  * \- banks;

  * \- exchange facilities having control or jurisdiction over us;

  * \- third parties in connection with the provision of our services for you;

  * \- electronic search providers for carrying out anti-money laundering and sanction checks;

  * \- SOCA (Serious Organized Crime Agency), to investigate or prevent fraud or other illegal activities in case suspicion arises about money laundering or terrorist financing.

MayzusFS may have to give your personal information to persons(s) or organizations located in countries outside EEA (European Economic Area) that do not have laws to protect customers’ personal information. 

#### 2\. Types of information required

The most general types of information Mayzus Financial Services requires are customers’ up-to-date proof of address, name, date of birth, sex, and telephone number. Corporate entities will also be asked for a copy of their memorandum and articles of association, list of current shareholders and director’s last annual return; ID and proof of address of beneficial owners; directors and powers of attorney, where applicable. 

#### 3\. Applications regarding customers’ data

The data protection legislation gives the customers the right to access the personal data that Mayzus Financial Services has about them.   
Unless there is a particular reason, Mayzus Financial Services approves customer requests regarding disclosure of their information to third parties after checking that the applicant is the person concerned. Additionally, in case of inaccurate information that we know about, we will apply the necessary changes to it.  
If you as a customer require information or require information to be disclosed to a third party, Mayzus Financial Services is entitled to charge you a minor fee for any administrative work and costs involved in producing this information. 

#### 4\. Customer inquiries and complaints

All customer inquiries regarding disclosure or correction of information should be directed to the following Mayzus Financial Services contact details: 

**Privacy Policy Inquiries:**

Tel: +44 (0) 208 956 2251  
Fax: +44 (0) 203 397 4818  

Mayzus Financial Services Ltd  
869 High Road,  
London, N12 8QA, UK

**Business hours:** 9.00 a.m. - 6:00 p.m.

(Business hours exclude weekends, public holidays and days for technical maintenance, of which customers will be informed in advance). 

#### 5\. Internet privacy

Our website uses cookies, which are used for storing site preferences and store data about your website usage, including your connection speed, details of your operating system, the time and duration of your visit and your IP address. The data collected by cookies enables us to keep our website updated and provides detailed information on the frequency and duration of visits to our website pages. We will not attempt to identify you from your IP address for any reason unless required to do so for legal purposes or to protect us or our customers' rights. 

You are using our website at your own risk, which means that we do not undertake any responsibility regarding the security of your personal data or any other sensitive information you shared via the Internet. We aim at maintaining a secure website with safest environment where all your data is stored in strictest confidence, however we are not liable for any of this data being intercepted and read by unauthorized parties. 

#### 6\. Maintenance and security

We preserve the right to monitor, record, store and use any telephone, email or other electronic communications with you for maintenance purposes, for the sake of re-checking any instructions you forward to us, and to improve the quality of our customer service. 

#### 7\. Money laundering and terrorist financing

MayzusFS may be required by statute to make a disclosure to the Serious Organized Crime Agency in case any transactions are suspected that involve money laundering or terrorist financing. In case of a disclosure related to your transactions, Mayzus Financial Services may not be able to inform you about it or about its reason, and will have to delay your transactions for a certain period of time. 

#### 8\. Consenting to our terms

By consenting to the terms and conditions described above, you agree to your data being shared outside the EU/EEA, where necessary. 

Authorized and regulated by FCA as Authorised Payment Institution under registration number 566505  
HM Revenue & Customs MLR No 12492642  
Data Protection Number Z2309500
